[Music]
[Música]
Something serious is also going to happen to the family
a pasar también algo fuerte en familia
and that is that Isabel Pantoja
y es que isabel pantoja
is going to take criminal action
va a tomar medidas penales
against
contra
the network.
la cadena
Okay,
vale
and they have issued
y es que han emitido
some audios. Well, here it says some audios
unos audios bueno aquí pone unos audios
but of course they are not audios, it is a
pero claro no son unos audios es una
call, it is a call that I do not know why
llamada es una llamada que no sé por qué
but a call that is, it is
pero una llamada que está que está
recorded, no, and it says
grabada no y dice
a call between Isabel Pantoja and
una llamada de isabel pantoja con
Encarna Sanchez 29 years ago, okay,
encarna sánchez hace 29 años vale
well, but I do not know if it is a call
bueno pero no sé si a una llamada
from her with Encarna or about Encarna,
de ella con encarna o sobre encarna
better said, about Encarna, that to a
mejor dicho sobre encarna eso a una
person she trusts,
persona de su confianza
okay, criminally, of
vale penalmente
course, because neither she nor the interlocutor
claro porque ni ella ni el interlocutor
has given permission, but of course
ha dado permiso pero claro
[Music]
[Música]
So how is that conversation going to come out,
entonces como a salir esa conversación
how are they having the conversation, one of
como tienen la conversación alguna de
the parties has had to give it
las partes las ha tenido que dar
a private conversation about
una conversación privada sobre asuntos
intimate matters of two people in which they have not
íntimos de dos personas en las que no
given consent nor are they a
han dado el consentimiento ni son
participant, no one there, well, it
partícipe nadie de ahí
is a package, but we have been in the
pues es un paquete pero estamos en la
same situation for
misma
years and years and years, here it is about whether it is
años y años y años aquí es sobre si se
admissible for processing
admite a trámite
and SAP and she did not know Encarna Sanchez,
y sap y no conoció encarna sánchez
but what program has the family followed, the
pero qué programa ha seguido familia
usual
el de siempre
Sálvame  Sálvame has brought to light some
sálvame sálvame ha sacado a la luz unos
audio recordings from almost three decades ago in
audios de hace casi tres décadas en lo
which Isabel Pantoja speaks openly about the
que isabel pantoja habla sin tapujos del
end of her friendship with Encarnación Sánchez. In other words,
final de su amistad con encarna sánchez
Isabel Pantoja is going to
o sea isabel pantoja va
think, if she wants a penny, to file a
pienso si una peseta quiera a denunciar
criminal complaint against Sálvame. No, no, not even where they have to
penalmente a sálvame no no ni a donde
give it. Where are you? Antonio David.
tienen que dar din estáis antonio david
Well, Antonella, I'm going to feel like a saint
pues antonella me voy a notar el santo
on that path and in chronicle
en esa vía y que en crónica
[Music]
[Música]